<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fabric Selects</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/users/jellysquid/</link><description>Recent content on Fabric Selects</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://fabric-selects.github.io/users/jellysquid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lithium</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/lithium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/lithium/</guid><description>Want to help support development?
Lithium is made possible thanks to the awesome supporters on my Patreon. Each pledge allows me to spend more time working on mods like these while helping to cover a few expenses. You&amp;rsquo;ll also gain some special perks on the official Discord server and access to prioritized support.
Server tick time (mspt) graph before and after installing Lithium. Measurements made in an existing world at a render distance of 18.</description></item><item><title>Phosphor</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/phosphor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/phosphor/</guid><description>Want to help support development?
Phosphor is made possible thanks to the awesome supporters on my Patreon. Each pledge allows me to spend more time working on mods like these while helping to cover a few expenses. You&amp;rsquo;ll also gain some special perks on the official Discord server and access to prioritized support.
Phosphor Phosphor is a Minecraft mod which works to optimize one of game&amp;rsquo;s most inefficient areas&amp;ndash; the lighting engine.</description></item><item><title>Sodium</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/sodium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/sodium/</guid><description>Sodium is made possible thanks to my supporters on Patreon, who help fund the time that goes into developing these mods. You won&amp;rsquo;t receive any special perks other than a badge of recognition, but you will get the nice feeling of supporting your favorite projects. You can click here or the button below to make a pledge to my page. Additionally, we have an official Discord server for all things related to my mods.</description></item></channel></rss>