<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mods on Fabric Selects</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/</link><description>Recent content in Mods on Fabric Selects</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cinderscapes</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/cinderscapes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/cinderscapes/</guid><description>Cinderscapes is a beautiful, yet frightening biomes mod for Minecraft 1.16 and above running on the Fabric mod loader. Cinderscapes enchances the default minecraft experience by adding 4 new rich and detailed nether biomes following in the same style as those already in the vanilla game. In addition to new biomes Cinderscapes adds some new unique types of building blocks further expanding your building capabilities.</description></item><item><title>CraftPresence</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/craftpresence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/craftpresence/</guid><description>CraftPresence Completely customize the way others see you play Minecraft via Discord&amp;rsquo;s Rich Presence API &amp;amp; the DiscordIPC API by jagrosh!
Port Notes Some versions of CraftPresence for Minecraft 1.14.x, 1.15.x, and 1.16.x require the FabricMC ModLoader Some versions of CraftPresence for Minecraft 1.13.x require the Rift ModLoader Features In addition to having the Ability to Change your Discord Status from &amp;ldquo;Playing Minecraft&amp;rdquo;, This Mod offers plenty of Customization Options to specify entirely how others see you play.</description></item><item><title>Fabric API</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/fabric-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/fabric-api/</guid><description>Fabric API is a cool mod that does stuff</description></item><item><title>Lithium</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/lithium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/lithium/</guid><description>Want to help support development?
Lithium is made possible thanks to the awesome supporters on my Patreon. Each pledge allows me to spend more time working on mods like these while helping to cover a few expenses. You&amp;rsquo;ll also gain some special perks on the official Discord server and access to prioritized support.
Server tick time (mspt) graph before and after installing Lithium. Measurements made in an existing world at a render distance of 18.</description></item><item><title>Mod Menu</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/mod-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/mod-menu/</guid><description>Mod Menu is a cool mod that does stuff</description></item><item><title>Phosphor</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/phosphor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/phosphor/</guid><description>Want to help support development?
Phosphor is made possible thanks to the awesome supporters on my Patreon. Each pledge allows me to spend more time working on mods like these while helping to cover a few expenses. You&amp;rsquo;ll also gain some special perks on the official Discord server and access to prioritized support.
Phosphor Phosphor is a Minecraft mod which works to optimize one of game&amp;rsquo;s most inefficient areas&amp;ndash; the lighting engine.</description></item><item><title>Sodium</title><link>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/sodium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fabric-selects.github.io/mod/sodium/</guid><description>Sodium is made possible thanks to my supporters on Patreon, who help fund the time that goes into developing these mods. You won&amp;rsquo;t receive any special perks other than a badge of recognition, but you will get the nice feeling of supporting your favorite projects. You can click here or the button below to make a pledge to my page. Additionally, we have an official Discord server for all things related to my mods.</description></item></channel></rss>